Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Hans Weissenstein Negatives PHOTOS 019 001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series XX: Schools/Students/Teachers.
  - Honor Picket Line PS 75 [Signs in English and Spanish; one reads "We go back at 8:30 today, but in September - all the way".], Mar 29, 1963 (Box 3, Item 7556)
  - Balloting Seward HS, Dec 4, 1963 (Box 3, Item 8010)
  - Robert] Atkin[s] Lecture PS 41, Apr 28, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8281)
  - Columbia University Retarded Children, Jun 6, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8425)
  - Camp Teachers Rally Washington Irving HS, Jul 29, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8473)
  - Guidance Teachers at Maritime Union, Sep 10, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8535)
  - Substitute Teachers at Board of Education, Sep 15, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8538)
  - Guidance Teachers Washington Irving HS, Sep 19, 1964 (Box 4, Item 8534)
  - Discussion Group PS 123 Queens, May 25, 1966 (Box 5, Item 9937)
  - PS 113 [meeting in school library], Dec 23, 1966 (Box 5, Item 10216)
  - PS 66 [Shots of unidentified teachers], Jan 11, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10229)
  - PS 113 [Portables demonstration; "Get rid of the portables. They're little more than -HUTS-" and "We need a wing for Quality Education" signs on a coach bus with women and children standing in front.], Feb 17, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10304)
  - 1st Bimonthly Checks PS 136, May 16, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10488)
  - Community Celebration PS 113 Percy Sutton, Jun 16, 1967 (Box 5, Item 10572)
  - PS 131 Picket, Jun 28, 1967 (Box 6, Item 10758)
  - Manhattan Boro Community College, Feb 7, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11044)
  - PS 130 Spr[ing] [African-American history day], Feb 9, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11050)
  - PS 96 [classes], May 3, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11175)
  - PS 40 Jamaica [classes], May 3, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11176)
  - Van Buren HS Jamaica [demonstration by Parent Teacher Coalition to restore funds cut from budget.], May 7, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11188)
  - PS 117 East 109 Street Picket, May 7, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11189)
  - PS 307 Washington [classes and posed pictures of teachers], May 8, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11201)
  - PS 11 Course, May 28, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11255)
  - Classes [being held at C. Rothman's apartment at] 270 Fulton Street, Nov 1, 1968 (Box 6, Item 11469)
  - PS Henry Street, Dec 2, 1968 (Box 30, Item 15593)
  - PS 205 Brooklyn letter Elections, Jan 8, 1969 (Box 6, Item 11585)
  - PS 497 Bronx Joan Fisher, Jan 13, 1969 (Box 6, Item 11590)
  - Howard Beach JHS 145 Bronx, Jan 13, 1969 (Box 6, Item 11589)
  - PS 113 Brooklyn District 19 [?] Harold Saltzman Lane HS, Jan 15, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11592)
  - District 15, John Jay HS, Jeanette DiLorenzo, Jan 20, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11605)
  - District 30, Joseph Shannon, New Dorp HS, Staten Island, Jan 20, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11606)
  - Eastirwin [?] Drive 116 Street, Benj. Franklin HS, No Quorum, Jan 21, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11613)
  - District 13 Sands Drive JHS, Pete O'Rourke, Will Farolson [?], Mike Levine, Jan 23, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11612)
  - Bayside HS, no quorum 26, Jan 23, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11614)
  - Parsons Jr. H.S., Sol Levine JHS 168, Sylvia Dansy PS 201 [?], Jan 24, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11615)
  - District 17 Clara Barton H. S. Lester Weinberg, Ed Muir, Erasmus, Jan 31, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11640)
  - District 2 Richman H.S. Ivan Tiger, Feb 2, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11641)
  - Ridge Street, Board of Education, H. S. Tutor Sure [?], Feb 7, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11651)
  - John Jay H.S. Story College Board, Feb 13, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11659)
  - Course PS 11 Jr. [?] Service [?], Feb 20, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11673)
  - PS JHS 10 District 23 Vinicio Donato, Feb 24, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11681)
  - PS 129 [Dr. Martin Luther] King Museum, Feb 24, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11675)
  - Brooklyn PTA/Teachers JHS 142, Mar 1, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11690)
  - PS 144, Mar 7, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11702)
  - HS Students / Dan Sanders [Eugene Kauffman Legal Office / Fern Midwood, Asst. S[?] / Debbie Isom], Mar 10, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11706)
  - PS 39 Pachelo [includes teacher seated at her desk in empty classroom and shots of protest signs written on the blackboard, including "Parents demand the teachers get out" and "Mr. Acosto is not wanted."], Mar 25, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11742)
  - Para-Professionals PS 182 Brooklyn, Mar 27, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11748)
  - PS 123 Queens Para-Professionals [& students], Apr 11, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11770)
  - PS 40 Queens Parent Teacher Luncheon, Apr 26, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11816)
  - PS 146 Open House, Apr 29, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11827)
  - Eiseman JHS Brooklyn Fiddler on the Roof, May 2, 1969 (Box 7, Item 11833)
  - PS 207, May 6, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11838)
  - Open House Fair PS 218, May 7, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11837)
  - PS 123 Queens [?], May 8, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11921)
  - Coronation MES 120 K, May 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11886)
  - MES Conf. PS 109, May 17, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11884)
  - May Festival PS 138, May 18, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11888)
  - PS 39 Party by PA to teachers, May 29, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11922)
  - PS 307 MES[?] Brooklyn, Jun 9, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11944)
  - PS 33 Manhattan Headshots Mrs. Long, Mrs. Ruiz, Jun 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11968)
  - PS 25 Julia Rogers - Doris Hunter, Jun 16, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11969)
  - Demonstration PS 67 Bronx, Jun 20, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11977)
  - School Fair PS 85 Bronx, Jun 20, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11976)
  - Delegate Assembly Fashion H.S., Jun 24, 1969 (Box 8, Item 11982)
  - PS 61 Manhattan Demonstration, Sep 8, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12034)
  - PS 211Bronx Dedication Bi-lingual, Sep 11, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12038)
  - Brooklyn In House Kindergarten [Students being taught in someone's home, next to the television and at the dining room table.], Sep 19, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12056)
  - PS 67 Bronx Vandalism, Sep 26, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12067)
  - Jamaica Jewish Center [students and teachers], Oct 1, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12081)
  - Damages Brooklyn - Portables [damage and graffiti at unnamed school], Oct 8, 1969 (Box 8, Item 12095)
  - Brandeis H. S. [meeting], Oct 20, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12124)
  - PS 6 Bronx Mini School, Oct 30, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12163)
  - PS 146 Bronx Rain Damage, Nov 5, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12170)
  - Julia Richmond H.S. play, Nov 6, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12172)
  - Vito, Washington Irving H. S. & Vigil, 260 Park, Nov 12, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12197)
  - PS 49 Bronx, Nov 12, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12191)
  - PS 49 Bronx [classes], Nov 14, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12199)
  - Lou Hert, Kansas City PS 146 + UFT, Nov 14, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12200)
  - IS 155 Bronx [classes] [Bulletin board at back of classroom reads: "New York: Is This Any Way to Run a City?" with pictures.], Nov 17, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12201)
  - Kindergarten PS 146, Nov 20, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12211)
  - Puerto Rican Festival PS 327, Nov 21, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12215)
  - School for the Deaf, Nov 24, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12230)
  - PS 307 Brooklyn Kids at Play [playing], Dec 16, 1969 (Box 9, Item 12284)
  - PS 50 Queens Table Group, Dec 23, 1969 (Box 10, Item 12308)
  - H.S. Art & Design. Statue of Dr. Martin L. King, Jan 22, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12341)
  - George Westinghouse Technical H.S. Brooklyn, Jan 22, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12339)
  - PS 219 Brooklyn Parents Workshop, Jan 26, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12359)
  - High School 142 Queens Debate, Jan 26, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12355)
  - Little Red School House, Jan 29, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12367)
  - Regent Scholars at Fordham, Feb 6, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12381)
  - PS 67 Photo & Typing Class, Feb 9, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12387)
  - PS 304 Bedford / Stuyvesant Food & [Black Heritage] Displays, Feb 11, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12388)
  - Boys HS & PS 99, Feb 11, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12389)
  - PS 129 Afro-American Week, Feb 20, 1970 (Box 10, Item 12402)
  - Brock Peters Awards IS 10 ["Welcome Home Brock Peters" sign; actor Brock Peters comes back to his old school[?]], Mar 6, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12425)
  - Para-Prof. At PS 47 [Mrs. Jeanette] DiLorenzo, Mar 10, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12430)
  - PS 129 Broglia West [Students reading Langston Hughes poetry, showing off African-American pictures, magazines and history posters.], Mar 12, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12440)
  - MES 307 Broadway [students performing "Hello Dolly"], Mar 20, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12449)
  - PS 20 Hunts Point Garbage, Mar 20, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12450)
  - PS 154 MES, Apr 6, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12485)
  - TV Taping PS 130, Apr 7, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12487)
  - PS 126 Early Childhood Miss Helen Ephros, Mrs. Marylin Barr, Raquel Zapata Para-Pro., Apr 8, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12491)
  - PS 33 Early Childhood Helen Lai, Marilyn Copeland, Apr 8, 1970 (Box 11, Item 12490)
  - PS 50 Queens Demonstration, Apr 9, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12498)
  - PS 155 Early Childhood, Apr 14, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12508)
  - PS 20 Queens Flushing, M Street, Small Group Learning, Apr 16, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12516)
  - PS 57 Bronx [Crotonave [?] Spanish [?]], Teaching English, Apr 16, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12515)
  - George Washington H. S. Press Conference, Apr 17, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12519)
  - JHS 142 DiLorenzo [school fair with students showing off their work], Apr 18, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12522)
  - PS 307 Earth Day, Apr 22, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12528)
  - District Math Workshop PS 307, Apr 23, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12539)
  - PS 50 Playground, Apr 24, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12536)
  - MES Sessions Chas. Evans Hughes H.S., Apr 25, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12538)
  - PS 60 Spanish Class for Parents, Apr 28, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12544)
  - PS 188 Sight Conservation Class, Apr 28, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12543)
  - Music & Art H.S., May 4, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12555)
  - James Monroe H.S. Narcotics Program Brotherhood Estate [?], May 19, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12595)
  - Jamaica H.S. Guidance Counselor[s], May 20, 1970 (Box 12, Item 12608)
  - PS 211 Brooklyn Demonstration, Jun 2, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12637)
  - PS 120 Brooklyn Crossing Queen, Jun 3, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12638)
  - Afro-American Exhibit Display PS 151, Jun 3, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12636)
  - Washington Irving H.S. Art Show, Jun 4, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12644)
  - PS 51 Bronx Graduation Activities, Jun 4, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12647)
  - MES courses PS 307 K, Jun 6, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12649)
  - PS 87 Manhattan Demonstration for more Teachers & Para-Pros., Jun 8, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12660)
  - PS 51 Bronx & School without Failures Kid [?] Psychologist & Reading Lab, Jun 8, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12652)
  - PS 207 Brooklyn Tree Planting, Jun 9, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12661)
  - PS 67 Brooklyn Experimental School [Collection includes corresponding print for negative frame #12653-18.], Jun 9, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12653)
  - Demonstration PS 198 [Third] Ave, Jun 9, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12659)
  - HS of Fashion - Para-Professionals District Coordinators, Jun 11, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12676)
  - JHS 43 Manhattan Happening Experim., Jun 12, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12680)
  - Mini School Opening Dedication PS 134, Jun 12, 1970 (Box 13, Item 12675)
  - PS 247 Brooklyn Mini School Demonstration, Jun 17, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12690)
  - Board of Education Brandeis HS Demonstration, Jun 17, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12693)
  - Carnival PS 332 Brooklyn, Jun 19, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12695)
  - PS 163 [teachers standing and talking], Aug 7, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12732)
  - Demonstration IS 44, Sep 21, 1970 (Box 14, Item 12765)
  - George Washington HS, Sep 28, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12783)
  - Demonstration PS 167 Brooklyn, Sep 28, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12780)
  - PS 11 City Hall, Sep 29, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12782)
  - Little Red School Middle School Opening, Sep 30, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12790)
  - PS 48 Bronx Boycott School, Oct 14, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12812)
  - PS 232 Bronx Converted Bowling Alley, Oct 19, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12821)
  - School for the Deaf opening, Oct 20, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12825)
  - Benjamin Franklin HS college bound, Oct 21, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12834)
  - Mr. Drut PS 57 Bronx Spanish Class, Nov 5, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12872)
  - EPS School PS 332 Brooklyn [classroom] [Collection includes corresponding prints for negative #'s 12876-5, 12876-26, 12876-30.], Nov 5, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12876)
  - PS 2 Childhood Center, Nov 13, 1970 (Box 15, Item 12890)
  - Villa Bianca HS Teachers Queens, Nov 16, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12897)
  - PS 70 Puerto Rican Discovery Day, Nov 17, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12898)
  - Puerto Rican Discovery Day - Taft HS, Nov 18, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12904)
  - Puerto Rico Day - 6 Schools Bronx, Nov 19, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12909)
  - John Dewey HS Fred Koury, Nov 20, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12912)
  - PS 45 Brooklyn [singing], Nov 23, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12917)
  - PS 146 Bronx [hallways, exterior], Nov 30, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12925)
  - PS 186 Manhattan Demonstration & Meeting & Old Building, Dec 1, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12929)
  - PS 111 Morris HS Tour & Kingsbridge Armory Bronx, Dec 4, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12940)
  - Abe Levine & Sy Schwartz touring corridor classrooms PS 144 Manhattan, Dec 8, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12943)
  - PS 3 Brooklyn Narcotics Program & Lecture, Dec 9, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12949)
  - Springfield Gardens High School [classroom], Dec 10, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12956)
  - IS 142 Queens Comm., Dec 17, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12978)
  - PS 151 Brooklyn [students in halls], Dec 17, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12974)
  - PS 335 Brooklyn Talent Show for Parents & Teachers, Dec 21, 1970 (Box 16, Item 12982)
  - Wagner JHS Reading Class, Jan 11, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13002)
  - MES 307 Visitors Wilmington Del, Jan 11, 1971 (Box 16, Item 12998)
  - Bronx Schools Martin Luther King Day, Jan 11, 1971 (Box 17, Item 12999)
  - Albert Shanker at Einstein School IS 131, Jan 11, 1971 (Box 16, Item 12997)
  - Instructional Resources Center PS 50 Queens, Jan 11, 1971 (Box 26, Item 13789)
  - Elementary Schools, Jan 12, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13005)
  - Howard Taft H.S. - Martin Luther King Exhibit & Performance, Jan 13, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13008)
  - IS 10 [teachers receiving] Checks, Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13011)
  - PS 50 Queens stop light demonstration, Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13010)
  - PS 208 - Martin L. King Celebration, Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13009)
  - IS 293 Brooklyn Nathan Hale Production [Appears to be a celebration of African heritage and culture - students participating in African dance and drumming.], Jan 14, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13014)
  - PS 127 Queens [singing], Jan 19, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13020)
  - Secretaries Action Committee - HS of Art & Design, Jan 21, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13026)
  - Walton HS Bronx Shanker Speech, Jan 22, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13028)
  - Chinese New Year PS 130, Jan 26, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13032)
  - JHS 218 Queens Albert Shanker Speech, Jan 27, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13038)
  - QuEST Program PS 181, Jan 27, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13039)
  - PS 181 Anne Kessler - Instructing, Jan 27, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13036)
  - Taft HS [Al] Shanker Speaking, Jan 28, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13041)
  - PS 23 Manhattan Chinese New Year Play, Jan 28, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13042)
  - John Brown HS Martin L. King Display, Jan 29, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13043)
  - PS 94 School Secretaries (office), Feb 1, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13045)
  - PS 95 Bronx District 10, Feb 3, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13050)
  - MES 102 Bronx People in Workshop, Feb 5, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13054)
  - JHS 17 Manhattan Drug Out, Feb 5, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13055)
  - PS 147 Queens Boycott Overcrowding [?], Feb 8, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13056)
  - PS 284 Brooklyn Kindergarten & Reading Program, Feb 8, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13061)
  - PS 332 Brooklyn Black Music through the Years, Feb 8, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13062)
  - Albert Shanker Speaking - Erasmus HS, Feb 9, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13063)
  - PS 75 Bronx Open House, Feb 11, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13069)
  - JHS 232 Brooklyn Black History Program, Feb 11, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13072)
  - PS 271 Brooklyn Bi-Lingual workshop, Feb 11, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13068)
  - PS 159 Brooklyn Black History Celebration, Feb 11, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13070)
  - IS 131 Bronx Portable Museum, Feb 16, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13073)
  - JHS 57 K Brooklyn Picket line, Feb 18, 1971 (Box 17, Item 13079)
  - PS 45 Queens - Negro History - Performance for parents, Feb 23, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13093)
  - District 6 PS 186 City Hall Rob Miller, Feb 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13097)
  - PS 262 Brooklyn Demonstration, Feb 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13094)
  - District 6 PS 186 Boycott, Feb 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13096)
  - John Dewey HS Brooklyn Committee Meeting, Feb 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13095)
  - Scholarship Awards Fordham University, Feb 26, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13104)
  - PS 165 Manhattan NYC Puerto Rico Visitors, Feb 26, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13102)
  - 196 K Teacher - Mom Program Brooklyn [Collection includes corresponding print for negative # 13112-1.], Mar 3, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13112)
  - HS Music & Arts Poster Making, Mar 10, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13132)
  - JH 60 - Tin cans for recycling & Mr. Possikoft, Mar 15, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13147)
  - JHS 51 - Albert Shanker Speaking - Staten Island, Mar 17, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13151)
  - Wagner JHS 167 Lovers & Other Strangers, Mar 18, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13157)
  - PS 112 Early Childhood Preschool, Mar 18, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13155)
  - PS 29 District 15 Meeting - Brooklyn, Mar 24, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13170)
  - HS Design & Art Panel Discussion S[andy] Feldman, Mar 25, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13167)
  - IS 318 Teacher Training Institute - Brooklyn, Mar 25, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13169)
  - Kings County Comm. College Para-Pros., Mar 29, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13175)
  - PS 31 Open House Bronx, Mar 29, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13172)
  - Music Courses in Brooklyn Schools, Mar 30, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13174)
  - PS 9 Brooklyn Drug Program, Mar 30, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13173)
  - MES 307 The Me Nobody Knows, Apr 2, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13185)
  - IS 88 [meeting], Apr 2, 1971 (Box 18, Item 13188)
  - Westinghouse HS Educational skill B[rooklyn], Apr 5, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13193)
  - PS 396-327 Brooklyn Fiesta Panamerica, Apr 6, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13195)
  - ILGWU [International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union] HQ School Group - Shop visit, Apr 7, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13197)
  - IS 80 Bronx Drug Program for JHS Students, Apr 19, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13280)
  - IS 80 Bronx Drug Program for JHS students, Apr 19, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13280)
  - Dan Sanders at Fordham, Apr 20, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13213)
  - PS 206 Brooklyn Chapter Meeting, Apr 21, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13215)
  - PS 70 Bronx Drug Program, Apr 21, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13214)
  - Para-Professional Teacher PS 35, Apr 22, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13223)
  - IS 162 Bronx New School Opening, Apr 23, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13218)
  - JHS 296 Brooklyn Pan American Show, Apr 23, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13219)
  - PS 35 Visited by PS 45 Brooklyn, Apr 23, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13220)
  - Parents Recognition Day - PS 155 Manhattan, Apr 27, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13241)
  - JHS 136 Brooklyn - Musical Comedy - "The Happy Attitude", Apr 28, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13244)
  - PS 90 Brooklyn Dance Demonstration, Apr 29, 1971 (Box 19, Item 13243)
  - PS 2 Visit by [Ted] Britton Britain's AAlbert Shanker, Apr 29, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13255)
  - PS 104 Bronx Opening of annex, Apr 30, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13259)
  - PS 130 Manhattan Chinese - Puerto Rican - Day, Apr 30, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13253)
  - School on the Rocks, Apr 30, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13254)
  - JHS 141 Bronx Symposium on Environment, Apr 30, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13258)
  - District 16 Auxiliary Training Center, May 3, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13260)
  - Maxwell Evening HS Center Brooklyn Educational Program, May 4, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13263)
  - PS 150 Bronx Crop Principal Black & Puerto Rican Culture, May 5, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13264)
  - JHS 142 Brooklyn Demonstration, May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13265)
  - PS 9 Brooklyn open Sesame Street [play], May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13266)
  - PS 196 Queens overcrowded classes - demonstration, May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13267)
  - Chapter Chairman H. S. [of] Fashion [Industries], May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13269)
  - Rally Francis Lewis HS Queens, May 6, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13271)
  - Rikers Island Prison PS 189, May 7, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13272)
  - IS 316 Brooklyn Para-Professional Bonnie Durden, May 10, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13278)
  - St. Mary's Hospital - PS 335 Brooklyn Peter Pan, May 10, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13279)
  - PS 167 Brooklyn Blocking Eastern Parkway Service Rd., May 10, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13277)
  - Robert Wagner JHS Variety Show, May 11, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13288)
  - PS 396 Brooklyn Open House Exhibit, May 12, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13292)
  - JHS 111 Brooklyn Career Day, May 12, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13293)
  - PS 20 Brooklyn Crowded Classes & Motorcade Boro Hall, May 13, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13294)
  - PS 134 Queens w/ A. L. Hollis Open House, May 14, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13298)
  - Morris HS Principal Guard ___ [?], May 14, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13299)
  - PS 31 Bronx Boy Scout Sleep-in, May 14, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13301)
  - PS 298 Brooklyn Pre-Kindergarten Program, May 14, 1971 (Box 20, Item 13297)
  - Reading Classes PS 130 Bronx Paul Gershwin, May 17, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13311)
  - Fair PS 226 Manhattan AMIC 71 str., May 18, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13314)
  - Seward Park HS Music Festival, May 19, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13316)
  - PS 150 Brooklyn science fair, May 19, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13317)
  - Julia Richmond HS $12,000 check Football Team, May 20, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13324)
  - PS 2 M Trilingual show, May 21, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13325)
  - AAEU District 8 [basketball], May 21, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13330)
  - JHS 252 Brooklyn Fashion show, May 22, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13331)
  - PS 128 M King Film Premiere - Para-Professional - PS 128 M, May 22, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13332)
  - Ed. Conf. PS 154 M, May 22, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13333)
  - House Economics PS 294 Brooklyn, May 26, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13343)
  - Maxwell Vocational HS Fashion show, May 26, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13351)
  - PS 286 Brooklyn [classroom], May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13355)
  - PS 2 Queens Dance Festival, May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13357)
  - Washington Irving HS Art Show, May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13345)
  - PS 218 School Fair Brooklyn, May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13349)
  - Art Show PS 244 Brooklyn, May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13348)
  - Puppet Show PS 205 Brooklyn, May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13346)
  - PS 284 Brooklyn Health Fair, May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13350)
  - PS 136 Bronx Play Carol Landau [?], May 27, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13356)
  - Bronx Joan Fischer PS 30 Dance - PS 49 Trilingual - PS 65 Hansel & Gretel - JHS 139, May 28, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13359)
  - PS 116 Brooklyn Health Fair, May 28, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13363)
  - PS 23 Mini School Opening Ribbon Cutting, Jun 2, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13366)
  - Maxwell Vocational HS Wartburg Lutheran Hospital Albert Shanker, Jun 2, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13374)
  - PS 1 Career Program, Jun 3, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13373)
  - School for Deaf Art Exhibit, Jun 3, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13368)
  - District 12 Concert Alice Tully Hall, Jun 4, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13375)
  - MES Conference PS 154, Jun 5, 1971 (Box 21, Item 13372)
  - 300 Scholarships at Julia Richmond [?], Jun 8, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13384)
  - PS 128 Bronx District Show Awards & Exhibit, Jun 9, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13389)
  - PS 274 Brooklyn Speakers, Jun 9, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13390)
  - PS 271 Brooklyn - Panel Session, Jun 10, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13391)
  - PS 190 Art Show, Jun 14, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13397)
  - PS 94 Brooklyn Para-Professional - Paycuts[?] Party, Jun 15, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13398)
  - PS 99 Brooklyn Woodworking [and] Mass Production [classes], Jun 15, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13399)
  - PS 125 Brooklyn Kindergarten Graduation, Jun 16, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13400)
  - PS 25 Brooklyn Art Show, Jun 16, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13401)
  - Art Show PS 316 Brooklyn, Jun 18, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13413)
  - La Salle Jr. HS [PS 11?] Demonstration [Students and adults with signs reading "PS11 needs its MES program!" and "Confucius says: One MES school is better than none".], Jun 22, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13430)
  - PS 183 Play, Jun 23, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13428)
  - PS 169 Awards, Jun 23, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13429)
  - PS 221 - Play Hamlet, Jun 23, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13431)
  - IRS [IS?] 218 Scholarships, Jun 24, 1971 (Box 22, Item 13433)